Armin.
It's nice that I could be
a "good person" for you.
For now, you've won your bet.
But
my bet
begins now!
We believe we've found out
who the Female Titan is.
Her name is...
Annie!
A FEW DAYS AGO
What's taking so long?
Where the hell are Erwin's men?
At this rate, the Military Police Regiment
escort is going to show up before them.
Must be having a hell of
a hard time taking a shit.
You're very talkative today, Captain.
Don't be stupid.
I talk a lot.
I'm sorry.
If only I hadn't made
the wrong choice then,
none of this would have happened.
I told you. No one knows
how things will turn out.
-Sorry, I'm late.
-Not at all.
Guys!
Well...
We believe we've found out
who the Female Titan is.
What?
We will capture her this time.
We will do it the day after tomorrow,
while passing through Stohess District
on our way to the capital.
This will be our first
and last chance to capture her.
Once on the other side,
the government will take custody of Eren,
and we'll have difficulty investigating
those bent on destroying the Walls.
Both of which will foster
mankind's destruction.
We'll have to bet everything
on this operation.
This is the plan.
While passing through Stohess,
we use Eren as bait
to lure the target
into this underground passage
Given the target's size and strength,
if we can get her as far down as possible
we should be able to
immobilize her in her Titan form.
But in the event that
she transforms before then,
it will be up to you, Eren.
Yes, sir!
Are we certain the target
will actually be in Stohess then?
Yes. The target is a member
of the Military Police Regiment.
The Military Police Regiment?
It was Armin who identified her.
We believe that she killed
the two Titans we caught alive
and that she might have trained with you
in the 104th Cadet Corps.
Hold on a minute.
The 104th Cadet Corps...
The name of the girl we believe
to be the Female Titan is...
You can't be serious.
Annie Leonhart.
Oh, no.
Damn! That ring...
She knew I was lying from the very start!
She saw the ambush
coming from a mile away!
Surely, there must have been a better way!
Save the regrets for later!
What should we do now?
First, we rendezvous with
the 3rd Squad and get above ground.
Then we fight Annie,
the Female Titan, as per plan B!
Eren, you'll help catch her
in your Titan form, just as we planned.
All right?
Yes!
Hey!
It's the 3rd Squad!
Plan A failed?
It did!
Please switch to the backup plan!
She stomped through it?
-We have to help them!
-Eren!
Get back!
Hey! Mikasa!
Does she not care if she kills Eren?
She took a gamble.
She gambled on Eren surviving
when she made that hole.
This makes her all the more formidable!
Annie is that desperate to catch Eren now!
Now what?
Our escape route has been cut off.
And she'll be ready, waiting for us
if we make a run for it
using our omnidirectional mobility gear.
That said...
If we stay here, there's no telling
when she'll stomp on us.
I'll manage somehow!
Just like when I stopped that cannonball!
-Come here!
-Hey...
Here goes! Stay close!
What?
Again?
Damn it!
Of all times...
Damn, that hurt!
You can't transform
without a clear goal, right?
Try to focus again! Hard!
I'm trying to!
But it's not...
Are you sure?
Could it be you still have qualms
about fighting Annie?
Eren?
After all this,
don't tell me you still think
that Annie can't possibly
be the Female Titan.
Didn't you see that just now?
She killed our comrades, you know.
Do you still think it's not her?
Give me a break!
I'm trying here!
Annie is the Female Titan?
What makes...
what makes you think that, Armin?
The Female Titan knew
what you looked like from the start.
Plus, she reacted to
your nickname of "suicidal maniac,"
something only our classmates would know
But the primary reason
is that I believe she killed
the test subjects, Sawney and Beane.
How do you know that?
Killing them would have required
real skill,
so she would have used
the omnidirectional mobility gear.
Yes, but they held
that equipment inspection.
Annie's was fine.
Because she presented Marco's gear.
That's how she avoided being caught.
What?
What are you saying?
What has Marco got to do with this?
I'm not sure.
Maybe you just saw wrong?
No, I definitely recognized--
Hey, kid.
We get it.
Do you have any concrete evidence?
No, sir.
Personally, I think Annie
and the Female Titan look alike.
What? Are you crazy?
What kind of evidence is--
So basically,
we're going after her without proof.
Without proof?
You can't be serious.
Why?
What if it isn't Annie?
If it isn't Annie,
then she'll be cleared of suspicion.
I'll feel bad for causing her trouble
if that happens.
But
if we do nothing, the government
will make a sacrificial victim out of you.
You guys are crazy for doubting Annie.
Eren.
Does this talk about Annie ring any bells?
You fought hand-to-hand with
the Female Titan.
Did you see her use
any techniques only Annie uses?
You've realized, haven't you?
You've realized that
the Female Titan is Annie.
Then you know you have to fight.
Or are there certain,
special feelings stopping you?
What?
I have a plan!
Mikasa and I will exit that hole
and that entrance at the same time.
At that point,
Annie will go for one of us.
When she does, run the opposite way, Eren!
Wait!
That means one of you will get killed!
If we stay here, all three of us will die!
Mikasa! Get in position!
Right! I'll take this way!
Mikasa!
Armin!
How...
how are you guys able to fight?
How?
We don't have a choice.
We live in a cruel world.
Eren!
Annie! I won't let you have Eren!
I'm coming!
Open your eyes!
Don't let the Female Titan escape!
We can't let her get away!
What's going on?
Escort Squad! I'll hold this position!
See what's happening!
Understood!
Something is up.
First, there was that big explosion,
and now...
Nile!
Deploy all troops immediately.
We should assume a Titan has appeared.
Are you crazy?
This is Wall Sina, you know!
No Titan would show up here!
Halt! Stop right there, Jaeger!
I'm done playing dress-up!
Never call me that name again,
you halfwit!
Commander! I want to help too!
Ask the 4th Squad for equipment.
Understood!
Bravado is nice and all,
but just remember to stay alive.
Yes, sir!
What?
Erwin! What the hell was that?
Commander! I brought it!
-Good work.
-Thank you, sir!
Hold on, Erwin!
All able-bodied soldiers, follow me!
We're going to rendezvous
with the Capture Squad!
Erwin!
Stop!
You're committing a clear act of treason
against the Royal Government!
Nile, are you as rubbish-brained
as you look?
You don't seem to understand
what's happening here.
Remove your gear, Erwin!
There's a Titan!
-What is it doing here?
-What about the Wall?
Hey. That's a Titan, right?
Yes? Why?
Out of the way!
Just look at them, not giving a crap!
And to think
that could have been me up there too.
Man, what got into me?
Damn!
Don't try to kill her!
We just need to stop her!
It's no use! She's familiar with
the omnidirectional mobility maneuvers!
I won't make this easy for you!
Eren! Say something!
Eren!
Hey! What the hell are you doing?
Jean! Eren is stuck under here!
What? Wasn't he supposed to
turn into a Titan?
He couldn't!
I think the fact that the Female Titan
is Annie is holding him back.
What?
For now, we have to help him!
Jean! Give me a hand!
He couldn't do it?
Damn it, Eren! Quit screwing around!
I told you we would need
to count on you someday!
We're forced to put the world, humans,
and our own lives in your hands,
and this is all you have to show for it?
Marco didn't... Marco can't have...
Damn it!
Eren.
It's no use! We have to do
something about her first!
Eren.
There's something I told Jean once.
Those who can't abandon anything
can't change anything.
The ability to give up your humanity
when forced to rise above monsters,
I think that's something Annie can do.
Although, I don't know why she does it.
But
whoever can do that will prevail!
Annie!
If you don't kill me this time,
your sore excuses about "your real
bet starting now" will be worthless!
Armin! This way!
Understood!
-She's coming...
-Section Commander.
You have that crazy look in your eyes.
All right!
Personally, I thought having
a plan C seemed like overkill.
But Commander Erwin
really does know his stuff.
Now, then...
I suggest you be
a good girl and behave yourself.
You can't call any Titans
to eat you this time.
But don't worry.
I'll savor the information
that I'll pry from you instead.
She broke free?
Looks like we didn't set enough traps!
Don't let her escape! After her!
Those who can't abandon anything
can't change anything!
I know.
I failed before
when I clung to my friends
and the bond we shared.
Think back.
I'm going to drive them out.
No.
Kill them!
There's no time to think
whether it's right or wrong.
Just act.
Don't try to end things all nice and neat!
Yes.
Mikasa!
We live in a cruel world!
Now what?
Eren!
Eren.
"I'm going to drive out
every last Titan from this world."
The anger that drove young Eren
to make that vow that day
now drives him to destroy everything.